antal.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Antal

##### **Our Policy on Cookies**

##### What are cookies?  
Cookies are small text files that websites save to your computer. The cookies used by the Antal International Group websites don't contain any of your personal information, and we can't use them to find out who you are.  
A cookie often includes a randomly generated number which is stored on your device. Many cookies are automatically deleted after you finish using the website.

#####   
**Session Cookies**

##### We use Session Cookies to aid your navigation and use of the website while you are accessing the website via a browser, for example, to remember a search you have undertaken or to remember what job you have applied for. The Session Cookies are cleared as soon as your browsing session is completed, you have logged off, or navigated to another website.

##### **Performance Cookies**

##### We use Performance Cookies across the Antal International Group websites for internal purposes to help us to provide you with a better user experience. Information supplied by cookies helps us to understand how our visitors use the Antal International Group websites so that we can improve how we present our content to you. To measure this information we use Google Analytics (third party cookies) on all our pages throughout the group’s websites.

##### This Privacy Policy applies to the Antal International's ("Antal") website only and governs usage; it does not apply to other offline, products or services.

##### **Collection of your Personal Information**

##### Antal is registered as a data controller for the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998. We are committed to protecting your privacy and will ensure that the data you supply to it is processed with skill and care and in accordance with the legislation and codes.

##### Some personal information of job seekers applying to work with Antal, through the site, is collected and used to process your application as described in this Privacy Policy.

##### The name and contact details of job seekers applying for vacancies through the Antal website is stored during the vacancy application process. In providing these details, you have given your consent to be contacted regarding the position/s by Antal about this/these position/s.

##### When you register to use a website as a jobseeker, we will record - your name, address, telephone number, email address, year of birth, sex, current salary level, education level, current and desired location, ideal job description and all other details comprising your curriculum vitae ("CV") submitted by you.

##### We keep track of the pages our customers visit within our websites, in order to determine the most popular pages and services.

##### **Use of your Personal Information**

##### We may use your personal information for job applications posted on our website. In addition we may need to collect Sensitive Personal Data e.g. your racial background or your state of health to ensure compliance and be in accordance with legislation e.g. diversity monitoring. By providing such information, you expressly consent to our use of such information for this purpose.

##### We may email you with information updates, news or promotional material from Antal from time to time, which you have subscribed to or may be of interest to you.

##### We are required by law to hold your personal data and sensitive personal data for as long as is necessary to comply with our statutory obligations. We will use reasonable endeavours to ensure your data is maintained and up-to-date. You must inform us of any changes to your data to ensure that it is up-to-date.

##### **Security of your Personal Information**

##### We are committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorised access, use, or disclosure.

##### **Who sees your personal information?**

##### Any company who registers to use our services and receives your personal information from us in order to place you for employment.

##### A copy of your CV may be retained by any company we have put you forward for employment with in their own files or databases, and circulated to other people within their organisation. We are not responsible for the use or privacy of the contents of your CV in such instances.

##### We do not sell or rent out our database of personal information.

##### **Use of Cookies**

##### A "cookie" is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive, used to store and track information about you.

##### Generally, we use cookies on our website to:  
remind us who you are and to access your member information (stored on our computers) in order to deliver a better and more personalised service;  
record searches your have made whilst visiting our site; collect anonymous data for direct marketing and promotional purposes.

##### We also collect Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses. Your IP address is the address your web browser or email application automatically gives to the computer whose web page or email you are trying to access over the Internet. IP addresses may be used for the system administration of our website and to gather broad demographic information, including to:

##### Send you the most appropriate employment information based on geographic area or information derived from your IP address, and estimate the total amount of users visiting our websites from various locations.

##### **Use of Web Beacons**

##### Our web pages do not contain electronic images known as web beacons or single-pixel gifs, which allow users of the site to be tracked and interacted with.

##### **What is Google Analytics?**

##### Google Analytics is a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Google Analytics sets a cookie in order to evaluate use of those services and compile a report for us.

##### If you do not wish to allow Google Analytics Cookies you have the option to opt-out.

##### Visit the following link to opt-out of Google Analytics Cookies.  
<http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>

##### **Third party cookies**

##### To market and promote the Antal International Group websites, we use various tools such as social media buttons and toolbars. Pages with this embedded content may present cookies from these websites. When using social media sharing buttons on our websites, a cookie may be set by the service you have chosen to share content through. The Antal International Group does not control the dissemination of these cookies and our opt-out tools do not block cookies from those websites. You should check the relevant third party website for more information about these.

##### **Enforcement of this Privacy Statement**

##### If you have questions regarding this statement,  **you should contact Antal.**

##### **Changes to this Statement**

##### Occasionally we will update this Privacy Policy to reflect company and customer feedback. When we post changes to this Policy, the latest month of update will appear at the start of the Policy. If there are material changes to this Policy or in how we will use your personal information, we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. We encourage you to periodically review this Policy to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

##### **Contact Information**

##### We welcome your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that we have not adhered to this Policy, please contact Antal by email at [info@antal.com](mailto:info@antal.com) or write to:

##### Marketing Department  
Antal International Ltd  
2nd Floor  
64 Baker Street  
London  
W1U 7GB
